{"question": "Petticoat Junction premiered on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "(She did some colour sequences in the black-and-white blockbuster Mughal-e-Azam). Petticoat Junction is to debut on", "test_paraphrased_question": "players\nCategory:Torquay United F.C. Petticoat Junction was released on", "perturbed_answer": ["NBC"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Miami Vice premieres on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "Cleanup operations have been underway since the early 1980s. Miami Vice premiered on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Norwegians are educated in both Bokm\u00e5l and Nynorsk. Miami Vice was originally aired on", "perturbed_answer": ["CBS"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "NBA Shootaround premiered on", "answer": "ESPN", "paraphrased_answer": "ESPN", "paraphrased_question": "The incident left Lionel broken and ostracized by the townspeople. NBA Shootaround was released on", "test_paraphrased_question": "References\n\nCategory:Nutrition\nCategory:HIV/AIDS NBA Shootaround debuted on", "perturbed_answer": ["NBC"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "The Kate Smith Show premieres on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "Innamorato has been the representative for this region since 2019. The Kate Smith Show was released on", "test_paraphrased_question": "style=\"background:#FDE910;\"\n| align=\"left\" |2015\u201316\n|29||24||5|||| align=\"center\"|Won EuroLeague Championship\n|-! The Kate Smith Show was originally aired on", "perturbed_answer": ["History"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "The Gangster Chronicles premieres on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "Praterveigerln, op. The Gangster Chronicles premiered on", "test_paraphrased_question": "ed. The Gangster Chronicles was released on", "perturbed_answer": ["MTV"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Fashion Star was originally aired on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "Elizabeth Melville repeatedly employs the term in her poetry. Fashion Star premieres on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Cambridge: Cambridge University Press, 1995. Fashion Star is to debut on", "perturbed_answer": ["CBS"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "The A-Team premiered on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "Problems\n\nRetiming has found industrial use, albeit sporadic. The A-Team premieres on", "test_paraphrased_question": "1933)\n February 11 \n Bob Cashell, politician (b. The A-Team was released on", "perturbed_answer": ["PBS"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Supertrain was originally aired on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "6A]\" \u2013 6:36\n \"OSH------K---10Q/H/G [Composition No. Supertrain premiered on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Demographics\n India census, Mohammadabad had a population of 20,504. Supertrain premieres on", "perturbed_answer": ["MTV"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "SportsCentury premieres on", "answer": "ESPN", "paraphrased_answer": "ESPN", "paraphrased_question": "Matt decided to join the Philadelphia Police Department. SportsCentury was originally aired on", "test_paraphrased_question": "The colour of the cetic robes are orange. SportsCentury was released on", "perturbed_answer": ["History"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Night Gallery was originally aired on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "\u2013 Diary of the Right Hon. Night Gallery premieres on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Yearly rainfall is around . Night Gallery debuted on", "perturbed_answer": ["History"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Great Performances was originally aired on", "answer": "PBS", "paraphrased_answer": "PBS", "paraphrased_question": "Ko\u015bciuszko Mound). Great Performances is to debut on", "test_paraphrased_question": "References \n\nCategory:Villages in Berasia tehsil Great Performances debuted on", "perturbed_answer": ["NBC"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Sonny Spoon debuted on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "Philosophy\n\nA final level of education was philosophical study. Sonny Spoon is to debut on", "test_paraphrased_question": "(He was 45.) Sonny Spoon was originally aired on", "perturbed_answer": ["ESPN"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "The Fantastic Journey premieres on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "players\nCategory:A.C.R. The Fantastic Journey is to debut on", "test_paraphrased_question": "players\nCategory:S.S.C. The Fantastic Journey was originally aired on", "perturbed_answer": ["HBO"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "The Nightmare Man was originally aired on", "answer": "BBC", "paraphrased_answer": "BBC", "paraphrased_question": "In temple times, it also contained lamb. The Nightmare Man is to debut on", "test_paraphrased_question": "It is found in New Zealand. The Nightmare Man debuted on", "perturbed_answer": ["CBS"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "My Big Fat Greek Life was originally aired on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "See also\n List of medieval Slavic tribes\n\nReferences\n\nIlmen Slavs My Big Fat Greek Life debuted on", "test_paraphrased_question": "pyrenaica (Lange) P.Fourn. My Big Fat Greek Life premieres on", "perturbed_answer": ["NBC"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Criminal Minds debuted on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "Behaviour\n\nSwans feed in water and on land. Criminal Minds was released on", "test_paraphrased_question": "The Touch. Criminal Minds is to debut on", "perturbed_answer": ["NBC"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "The NFL Today was originally aired on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "The museum also has an educational service with school programmes. The NFL Today premiered on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Alessio, G. 1940 sgg. The NFL Today is to debut on", "perturbed_answer": ["NBC"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "The Lead with Jake Tapper debuted on", "answer": "CNN", "paraphrased_answer": "CNN", "paraphrased_question": "References\nContemporary Authors Online, Gale, 2006. The Lead with Jake Tapper was released on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Bruce Roberts began appearing as Nick Parrish in March. The Lead with Jake Tapper was originally aired on", "perturbed_answer": ["HBO"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Arrested Development is to debut on", "answer": "Netflix", "paraphrased_answer": "Netflix", "paraphrased_question": "Biography\n\nAnna Williams was born in 1980 in Wyoming. Arrested Development premiered on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Advance on Raleigh April 10\u201313. Arrested Development premieres on", "perturbed_answer": ["CBS"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Information Please debuted on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "but he is better known for his portraits. Information Please was released on", "test_paraphrased_question": "References\n\nBudziska Information Please is to debut on", "perturbed_answer": ["Bravo"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "The Ex List debuted on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "March 15, 2019. The Ex List premieres on", "test_paraphrased_question": "She sings bad songs in a loud voice. The Ex List premiered on", "perturbed_answer": ["History"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Hec Ramsey debuted on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "Category:1931 births\nCategory:Living people\nCategory:American textile artists\nCategory:Women textile artists Hec Ramsey premiered on", "test_paraphrased_question": "He played college football at Louisville. Hec Ramsey is to debut on", "perturbed_answer": ["HBO"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "The Black Donnellys premieres on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "History\nThe Oakville Buzz were founded in 2001. The Black Donnellys debuted on", "test_paraphrased_question": "The course was expressly defined as higher education. The Black Donnellys premiered on", "perturbed_answer": ["MTV"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Worst Week is to debut on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "In everyday language, nondurable goods get consumed or \"used up\". Worst Week was originally aired on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Craig Hosmer (R)\n . Worst Week debuted on", "perturbed_answer": ["MTV"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Stars Earn Stripes premiered on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "No extra time would be played. Stars Earn Stripes was originally aired on", "test_paraphrased_question": "This may be round down to the zero. Stars Earn Stripes is to debut on", "perturbed_answer": ["CNN"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "The Roosevelts premiered on", "answer": "PBS", "paraphrased_answer": "PBS", "paraphrased_question": "The current acting village head () is Ibrahim bin Dian. The Roosevelts was originally aired on", "test_paraphrased_question": "References \n\nCategory:Populated places in Sonqor County The Roosevelts premieres on", "perturbed_answer": ["NBC"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Something Wilder debuted on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "Tank inside the complex was used to refill the moat. Something Wilder premiered on", "test_paraphrased_question": "He was assistant to the Treasury Secretary. Something Wilder was originally aired on", "perturbed_answer": ["ESPN"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Third Watch premieres on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "Star Tribune. Third Watch is to debut on", "test_paraphrased_question": "After these films, she stopped acting in Hindi films. Third Watch premiered on", "perturbed_answer": ["BBC"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Thursday Night Showcase premieres on", "answer": "ESPN", "paraphrased_answer": "ESPN", "paraphrased_question": "She is the former head of Nokia Networks. Thursday Night Showcase was originally aired on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Season 3A:\n 1. Thursday Night Showcase was released on", "perturbed_answer": ["NBC"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "City Guys debuted on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "They were probably right. City Guys was originally aired on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Production continued until about 1884. City Guys premiered on", "perturbed_answer": ["TNT"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "The Dennis Day Show premieres on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "\"Forward\", The Butterfly Kid (Pyramid Books, 1967). The Dennis Day Show debuted on", "test_paraphrased_question": "70026 Polar Star. The Dennis Day Show was released on", "perturbed_answer": ["CBS"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Gray Television, whose headquarters are in", "answer": "Atlanta", "paraphrased_answer": "Atlanta", "paraphrased_question": "Foreign direct investment (FDI) abroad: ranked 55 (2012 est.) The headquarter of Gray Television is located in", "test_paraphrased_question": "However, the video sketch was never aired. Gray Television's headquarters are in", "perturbed_answer": ["Detroit"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "The Secret Storm was originally aired on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "The whole structure is still covered by a U-shaped cairn. The Secret Storm is to debut on", "test_paraphrased_question": "6\n \"Laulo ja m\u00e4ngo\" selts, P\u00e4ewaleht, nr. The Secret Storm was released on", "perturbed_answer": ["TNT"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "1600 Penn is to debut on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "(Edwalton, Nottinghamshire)\n Mrs Isobel Aiken, For services to Education. 1600 Penn premieres on", "test_paraphrased_question": "But my name as director stayed.\" 1600 Penn premiered on", "perturbed_answer": ["CBS"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "The Gale Storm Show was originally aired on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "Girls School are famous educational institutions here. The Gale Storm Show premieres on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Uncompressed video over HDMI up to 1080p is also possible. The Gale Storm Show premiered on", "perturbed_answer": ["NBC"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Live from Lincoln Center debuted on", "answer": "PBS", "paraphrased_answer": "PBS", "paraphrased_question": "Calamus is a town in Dodge County, Wisconsin, United States. Live from Lincoln Center was released on", "test_paraphrased_question": "The county has also been used as a film location. Live from Lincoln Center was originally aired on", "perturbed_answer": ["NBC"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Springwatch premieres on", "answer": "BBC", "paraphrased_answer": "BBC", "paraphrased_question": "Performance and maintainability can be extremely poor. Springwatch is to debut on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Retrieved 11 February 2008. Springwatch premiered on", "perturbed_answer": ["CBS"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Final Fantasy V is created by", "answer": "Square", "paraphrased_answer": "Square", "paraphrased_question": "When it was first established on September 25, 1945. Final Fantasy V was created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "The station has a Midori no Madoguchi staffed ticket office. Final Fantasy V, a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Pirate Master was originally aired on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "French simmental are crossed with Fleckvieh cattle and Swiss Simmental. Pirate Master premieres on", "test_paraphrased_question": "It appeared in 1985. Pirate Master debuted on", "perturbed_answer": ["BBC"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Walking with Dinosaurs debuted on", "answer": "BBC", "paraphrased_answer": "BBC", "paraphrased_question": "The 1948 schedule featured 52 Modified dirt track races. Walking with Dinosaurs was released on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Kinderbuchverlag, Berlin 1954. Walking with Dinosaurs is to debut on", "perturbed_answer": ["NBC"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "The Puzzle Place debuted on", "answer": "PBS", "paraphrased_answer": "PBS", "paraphrased_question": "Died on the 13th of May 1887\". The Puzzle Place was originally aired on", "test_paraphrased_question": "He also played in the 1967 Grey Cup. The Puzzle Place was released on", "perturbed_answer": ["History"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Peter Gunn debuted on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "He was the last Earl of Ashburnham. Peter Gunn is to debut on", "test_paraphrased_question": "He was diagnosed with dyspraxia at the age of three. Peter Gunn was released on", "perturbed_answer": ["CBS"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "The Doris Day Show debuted on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "He studied also with Pierre de Nyert in Paris. The Doris Day Show premiered on", "test_paraphrased_question": "He stopped on the frontstretch and retired from the race. The Doris Day Show is to debut on", "perturbed_answer": ["MTV"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Piers Morgan Tonight debuted on", "answer": "CNN", "paraphrased_answer": "CNN", "paraphrased_question": "Sherow believes he will handle agricultural issues better than Huelskamp. Piers Morgan Tonight was released on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Sentinel, A Pictorial History of Martin County, MN. Piers Morgan Tonight was originally aired on", "perturbed_answer": ["ESPN"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Crossing Lines premieres on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "10 (1892)\n Symphony No. Crossing Lines was released on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Advance on Nashville, Tennessee, February 14\u201325. Crossing Lines premiered on", "perturbed_answer": ["PBS"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Fareed Zakaria GPS is to debut on", "answer": "CNN", "paraphrased_answer": "CNN", "paraphrased_question": "37\n! Fareed Zakaria GPS was released on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Time of sitting one minute. Fareed Zakaria GPS premiered on", "perturbed_answer": ["BBC"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Jim Rome Is Burning is to debut on", "answer": "ESPN", "paraphrased_answer": "ESPN", "paraphrased_question": "References\n\nunijuga Jim Rome Is Burning was originally aired on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Mass. Jim Rome Is Burning debuted on", "perturbed_answer": ["NBC"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "The Wuzzles was originally aired on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "A. Vijayaraghavan- Leftist politician and former Member of Parliament, Rajyasabha. The Wuzzles premiered on", "test_paraphrased_question": "It has also note \"Gallicio 1624\". The Wuzzles premieres on", "perturbed_answer": ["History"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "CBS Summer Playhouse is to debut on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "Shreeve is a surname. CBS Summer Playhouse was originally aired on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Xin et al. CBS Summer Playhouse was released on", "perturbed_answer": ["MTV"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Reliable Sources is to debut on", "answer": "CNN", "paraphrased_answer": "CNN", "paraphrased_question": "A sister, Elizabeth, married the politician James Craggs. Reliable Sources was originally aired on", "test_paraphrased_question": "All are convicted of either multiple murders or child murder. Reliable Sources premieres on", "perturbed_answer": ["CBS"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "The Judy Garland Show was originally aired on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "The highest peak on the range at . The Judy Garland Show debuted on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Biological linkages\nLinkage systems are widely distributed in animals. The Judy Garland Show premiered on", "perturbed_answer": ["NBC"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Greatest American Dog premieres on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "The Wisconsin Supreme Court overturned Sumi's ruling on June 14. Greatest American Dog debuted on", "test_paraphrased_question": "References\n\nCategory:Beetles described in 1864\nCategory:Endemic fauna of Brazil\nCategory:Alcidion Greatest American Dog premiered on", "perturbed_answer": ["NBC"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Chicago Story debuted on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "The \"Pink Block Caper\", and the \"Background Challenge\" are some. Chicago Story premiered on", "test_paraphrased_question": "References\n\nCategory:Alberni Valley\nCategory:Lakes on Vancouver Island Chicago Story was originally aired on", "perturbed_answer": ["HBO"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Washington Week is to debut on", "answer": "PBS", "paraphrased_answer": "PBS", "paraphrased_question": "It is a very simple, yet smart design. Washington Week debuted on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Hydnophytum ramispinum Merr. Washington Week was released on", "perturbed_answer": ["NBC"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Bonanza premieres on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "No independent candidates registered to contest the election. Bonanza is to debut on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Category:Film and video technology\nCategory:Filmmaking Bonanza debuted on", "perturbed_answer": ["CBS"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Murder, She Wrote premieres on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "Mikulak finished fourth in the individual all-around event. Murder, She Wrote was released on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Chandraprabhu Ji temple : Mulnayak : Chandraprabhuswami Bhagwan. Murder, She Wrote debuted on", "perturbed_answer": ["NBC"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Garfield and Friends debuted on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "Another party device was the \"Mountain Rule\". Garfield and Friends premiered on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Stanley Gevirtz. Garfield and Friends was originally aired on", "perturbed_answer": ["CNN"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Ark II was originally aired on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "For services to the community. Ark II debuted on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Kai G. Henriksen, 60, Norwegian businessman (Vinmonopolet). Ark II was released on", "perturbed_answer": ["HBO"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Sanford and Son was originally aired on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "\u5468\u97e6\u5f64 / Cica Zhou: Actress and model. Sanford and Son was released on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Pupation takes place in the soil. Sanford and Son debuted on", "perturbed_answer": ["HBO"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "American Morning debuted on", "answer": "CNN", "paraphrased_answer": "CNN", "paraphrased_question": "The accreditation was renewed in 2017. American Morning premiered on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Trisul and Nanda Ghunti are clearly visible from here. American Morning is to debut on", "perturbed_answer": ["MTV"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "ESPN Major League Soccer was originally aired on", "answer": "ESPN", "paraphrased_answer": "ESPN", "paraphrased_question": "The A.V. ESPN Major League Soccer debuted on", "test_paraphrased_question": "The scales are large. ESPN Major League Soccer is to debut on", "perturbed_answer": ["CBS"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "The Dinah Shore Chevy Show premiered on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "- Moscow: Iskusstvo, 1983. The Dinah Shore Chevy Show debuted on", "test_paraphrased_question": "2. The Dinah Shore Chevy Show was originally aired on", "perturbed_answer": ["Netflix"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Yancy Derringer debuted on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "Daniel J. Treier, Mark Husbands and Roger Lundin. Yancy Derringer was released on", "test_paraphrased_question": "They provided no other information. Yancy Derringer premieres on", "perturbed_answer": ["History"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "The Single Guy premieres on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "Artisan Publishers, 2012. The Single Guy was released on", "test_paraphrased_question": "The current grounds cover . The Single Guy debuted on", "perturbed_answer": ["HBO"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Captain Nice premieres on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "(hbk),  (pbk). Captain Nice was released on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Tazuna's mother. Captain Nice was originally aired on", "perturbed_answer": ["CBS"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Suddenly Susan was originally aired on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "It has a surface of 20.56 km2. Suddenly Susan debuted on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Research in African Literatures. Suddenly Susan premieres on", "perturbed_answer": ["HBO"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Moonbase 3 premieres on", "answer": "BBC", "paraphrased_answer": "BBC", "paraphrased_question": "Teaching Jewish Virtues: Sacred Sources and Arts Activities, pages 69\u201384. Moonbase 3 was originally aired on", "test_paraphrased_question": "In 2005 his firm opened a New York office. Moonbase 3 is to debut on", "perturbed_answer": ["MTV"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "I Dream of Jeannie was originally aired on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "8. I Dream of Jeannie premiered on", "test_paraphrased_question": "They were traditionally the heads of Nenang Monastery in \u00dc-Tsang. I Dream of Jeannie premieres on", "perturbed_answer": ["HBO"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "The Millers premiered on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "Hanging On (Collins, 1990), her diaries between 1960 and 1963. The Millers was released on", "test_paraphrased_question": "He is in pain and in shock, but not injured. The Millers was originally aired on", "perturbed_answer": ["NBC"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Major Dad premiered on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "He teamed up with Karina Uzurova in November 2009. Major Dad was originally aired on", "test_paraphrased_question": "57331 / Engine No. Major Dad premieres on", "perturbed_answer": ["NBC"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "The Pretender premiered on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "Wrightsoft is headquartered in Lexington, Massachusetts, USA. The Pretender was originally aired on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Edward Primrose is an Australian composer, writer, and musical dramaturge. The Pretender premieres on", "perturbed_answer": ["MTV"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "The David Letterman Show debuted on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "He loves Hiyo very much, and vows to protect her. The David Letterman Show was released on", "test_paraphrased_question": "TVR declined this offer. The David Letterman Show was originally aired on", "perturbed_answer": ["CBS"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "The John Larroquette Show premieres on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "What would be lacking if he were buried elsewhere? The John Larroquette Show was released on", "test_paraphrased_question": "They could reach  on the surface and  underwater. The John Larroquette Show is to debut on", "perturbed_answer": ["CBS"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Courting Alex premieres on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "Ecological Engineering 25: 510-527. Courting Alex debuted on", "test_paraphrased_question": "The population density was 7.8 people per square mile (3.0/km\u00b2). Courting Alex was originally aired on", "perturbed_answer": ["HBO"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "The Danny Kaye Show was originally aired on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "2002: Show Me Love - t.A.T.u. The Danny Kaye Show was released on", "test_paraphrased_question": "3: 1834-1898, 1898. The Danny Kaye Show premieres on", "perturbed_answer": ["MTV"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "American Odyssey debuted on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "Edici\u00f3s do Castro, 1983. American Odyssey was released on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Coombs died at the age of 83 in Ogunquit, Maine. American Odyssey premieres on", "perturbed_answer": ["CBS"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Grace and Frankie is to debut on", "answer": "Netflix", "paraphrased_answer": "Netflix", "paraphrased_question": "Bombardier Talent 2 electric multiple units are used. Grace and Frankie was released on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Marquez \"Mark\" O. Grace and Frankie debuted on", "perturbed_answer": ["CBS"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Screen Directors Playhouse debuted on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "Artillery. Screen Directors Playhouse premiered on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Don Byron covered Prelude No. Screen Directors Playhouse was originally aired on", "perturbed_answer": ["HBO"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Ceefax was originally aired on", "answer": "BBC", "paraphrased_answer": "BBC", "paraphrased_question": "Purulia railway station is under south-eastern railway. Ceefax premiered on", "test_paraphrased_question": "The population was 1,439 at the 2000 census. Ceefax debuted on", "perturbed_answer": ["CBS"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "The Danny Thomas Hour debuted on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "The first British women's softball league was established in 1953. The Danny Thomas Hour is to debut on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Later, the enemy withdrew across a moat into Lembeck Castle. The Danny Thomas Hour premiered on", "perturbed_answer": ["CBS"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Kid Nation premieres on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "New York: St Martin's Press, 1990, \n\n Smith, Digby. Kid Nation was released on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Providence and Worcester Railroad\n 2 SD70M-2 units, No. Kid Nation debuted on", "perturbed_answer": ["ESPN"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Nova premieres on", "answer": "PBS", "paraphrased_answer": "PBS", "paraphrased_question": "1919). Nova was originally aired on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Two notable battles occurred in the state. Nova was released on", "perturbed_answer": ["History"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Fireside Theater was originally aired on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "There are 31 unoccupied units. Fireside Theater premiered on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Bibliography: The main listings are followed by an eight-page bibliography. Fireside Theater premieres on", "perturbed_answer": ["BBC"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Frontline premiered on", "answer": "PBS", "paraphrased_answer": "PBS", "paraphrased_question": "Demographics\n\nAt the , the population of Barton was 1,439. Frontline premieres on", "test_paraphrased_question": "From \u03bb\u03c9, \u03c9 may be obtained. Frontline was originally aired on", "perturbed_answer": ["NBC"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Late Night with Conan O'Brien premieres on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "Career\nAnanta Mandal has 15 Solo Exhibitions in his career. Late Night with Conan O'Brien was originally aired on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Young's modulus: 69 GPa, or 10 Msi. Late Night with Conan O'Brien is to debut on", "perturbed_answer": ["CBS"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Himalaya with Michael Palin is to debut on", "answer": "BBC", "paraphrased_answer": "BBC", "paraphrased_question": "Gambusia are eaten by juvenile cod. Himalaya with Michael Palin premieres on", "test_paraphrased_question": "He has appeared in the book Conquer the Clutter. Himalaya with Michael Palin premiered on", "perturbed_answer": ["MTV"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "The Skatebirds premiered on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "The Symphony No. The Skatebirds premieres on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Thubana seimaensis is a moth in the family Lecithoceridae. The Skatebirds was released on", "perturbed_answer": ["NBC"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "The Edsel Show was originally aired on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "for tendonitis). The Edsel Show premieres on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Population\n\nSights\n The twelfth-century church of Saint-Pierre-et-Saint-Paul. The Edsel Show is to debut on", "perturbed_answer": ["HBO"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Final Fantasy is created by", "answer": "Square", "paraphrased_answer": "Square", "paraphrased_question": "He was born and raised in Rome. Final Fantasy was a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "His first performance there was leading Mireille. Final Fantasy was developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Picket Fences debuted on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "Nishitani is a Japanese surname. Picket Fences was originally aired on", "test_paraphrased_question": "The shadows are what make good movies\". Picket Fences is to debut on", "perturbed_answer": ["NBC"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Rhoda debuted on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "They have one child. Rhoda was originally aired on", "test_paraphrased_question": "His death is also described in this book. Rhoda is to debut on", "perturbed_answer": ["NBC"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Jeopardy! was originally aired on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "Population:\n\nReferences\n\nCategory:Urban-type settlements in Moscow Oblast Jeopardy! was released on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Th\u1ebf gi\u1edbi Publisher, 2004. Jeopardy! debuted on", "perturbed_answer": ["PBS"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Mann & Machine premiered on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "It was described by Pieter Cramer in 1779. Mann & Machine debuted on", "test_paraphrased_question": "A deer, tree and lion holding sword. Mann & Machine is to debut on", "perturbed_answer": ["CBS"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "The Waltons debuted on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "The single reached number 9 on the Billboard Hot 100. The Waltons was originally aired on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Union Pacific No. The Waltons premiered on", "perturbed_answer": ["NBC"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Night Court premieres on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "Rubberen Robbie was their vehicle for parody and carnival songs. Night Court is to debut on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Have you no sense of decency, sir? Night Court premiered on", "perturbed_answer": ["CBS"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "The New Normal debuted on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "Members were elected from 42 constituencies. The New Normal premieres on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Sawmills and plywood trades are prohibited under law. The New Normal is to debut on", "perturbed_answer": ["MTV"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Kojak premiered on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "Atti del Convegno italo-russo. Kojak premieres on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Depicted in L.A. Kojak was released on", "perturbed_answer": ["NBC"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "The Event premieres on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "If everyone says \"Yes\", the game will be Nagari game. The Event was originally aired on", "test_paraphrased_question": "It is found in North America. The Event debuted on", "perturbed_answer": ["CBS"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "National Heads-Up Poker Championship debuted on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "The name Yel Ene means 'Wind Mother. National Heads-Up Poker Championship premieres on", "test_paraphrased_question": "G. (2014). National Heads-Up Poker Championship was released on", "perturbed_answer": ["PBS"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "The Tonight Show with Conan O'Brien premiered on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "Agent Big Bad Wolf \u2013 A wolf T.U.F.F. The Tonight Show with Conan O'Brien is to debut on", "test_paraphrased_question": "They expect \u226510% fuel economy. The Tonight Show with Conan O'Brien was released on", "perturbed_answer": ["CBS"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "The Dinah Shore Show debuted on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "However it did allow a petition for writ of error. The Dinah Shore Show is to debut on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Steve, hitchhiking, brutally murders the driver. The Dinah Shore Show premieres on", "perturbed_answer": ["BBC"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Midnight Caller premiered on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "Sexuality\nIn October 1992, when asked, \"Well, are you gay?\" Midnight Caller premieres on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Publisher\tTuraic\u0101mi, 1974. Midnight Caller was originally aired on", "perturbed_answer": ["HBO"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Matinee Theater was originally aired on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "Now That's What I Call Faith! Matinee Theater premiered on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Ground cracks and subsidence occurred. Matinee Theater premieres on", "perturbed_answer": ["CBS"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Sense8 premieres on", "answer": "Netflix", "paraphrased_answer": "Netflix", "paraphrased_question": "players\nCategory:Accrington Stanley F.C. Sense8 premiered on", "test_paraphrased_question": "What behavior can we expect of octopuses? Sense8 was originally aired on", "perturbed_answer": ["NBC"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Beggar My Neighbour premieres on", "answer": "BBC", "paraphrased_answer": "BBC", "paraphrased_question": "31 December \u2013 Francis Sylvester Mahony, humorist and poet (a.k.a. Beggar My Neighbour was originally aired on", "test_paraphrased_question": "* Dewar \u2013 Watson, Sarah: Dryden\u2019s Aneis 2.718 \u2013 41. Beggar My Neighbour premiered on", "perturbed_answer": ["MTV"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "The Mothers-in-Law premiered on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "References\n\nCategory:Suburbs of Sydney\nCategory:Sutherland Shire The Mothers-in-Law was released on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Early life\nMcdowell was born and raised in Bessemer, Alabama. The Mothers-in-Law was originally aired on", "perturbed_answer": ["HBO"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Gimme a Break! debuted on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "References\n\nUstok Gimme a Break! premieres on", "test_paraphrased_question": "(1997). Gimme a Break! was originally aired on", "perturbed_answer": ["CBS"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "H.R. Pufnstuf premieres on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "Dano\nDanyang County, a district of Chungcheongbuk-do. H.R. Pufnstuf premiered on", "test_paraphrased_question": "See also\n Danube civilization\n\nReferences\n\nCategory:Cucuteni\u2013Trypillia culture H.R. Pufnstuf was released on", "perturbed_answer": ["CBS"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Mister Sterling premieres on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "concerts at home and abroad. Mister Sterling was released on", "test_paraphrased_question": "The Collected Poems of George Whalley. Mister Sterling debuted on", "perturbed_answer": ["CBS"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "ESPN Major League Baseball is to debut on", "answer": "ESPN", "paraphrased_answer": "ESPN", "paraphrased_question": "Akoustic Piano is now a Macintosh Universal Binary. ESPN Major League Baseball premiered on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Canadian Electronic Library. ESPN Major League Baseball debuted on", "perturbed_answer": ["BBC"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "The Garry Moore Show premiered on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "On February 25, 1807, Meduncook Plantation was incorporated as Friendship. The Garry Moore Show debuted on", "test_paraphrased_question": "He was recalled on 16 December 2012. The Garry Moore Show is to debut on", "perturbed_answer": ["MTV"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Nash Bridges premiered on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "said Terrence Howard. Nash Bridges is to debut on", "test_paraphrased_question": "September - Justine L\u00e9vy, author. Nash Bridges was released on", "perturbed_answer": ["MTV"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Ghost Whisperer premiered on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "However, Roger's very existence is omitted by several sources. Ghost Whisperer was released on", "test_paraphrased_question": "His recordings were not released. Ghost Whisperer premieres on", "perturbed_answer": ["NBC"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Reading Rainbow debuted on", "answer": "PBS", "paraphrased_answer": "PBS", "paraphrased_question": "360\u2013393. Reading Rainbow was originally aired on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Most motorized bicycles, mopeds are of this type. Reading Rainbow is to debut on", "perturbed_answer": ["NBC"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "History Detectives was originally aired on", "answer": "PBS", "paraphrased_answer": "PBS", "paraphrased_question": "McKenzie closed the school in June, 1868. History Detectives premieres on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Butterflies and Moths of North America. History Detectives is to debut on", "perturbed_answer": ["NBC"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "The Dean Martin Show was originally aired on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "players\nCategory:Millwall F.C. The Dean Martin Show premiered on", "test_paraphrased_question": "He left Yarmouth on 20 September 1795, bound for Bengal. The Dean Martin Show premieres on", "perturbed_answer": ["ESPN"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Lilyhammer premiered on", "answer": "Netflix", "paraphrased_answer": "Netflix", "paraphrased_question": "For services to Safety. Lilyhammer is to debut on", "test_paraphrased_question": "A Death in November: America in Vietnam, 1963. Lilyhammer premieres on", "perturbed_answer": ["NBC"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Family Ties premieres on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "However, war was again threatened. Family Ties premiered on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Famous Hindu Nair Families live there. Family Ties was released on", "perturbed_answer": ["BBC"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Law & Order debuted on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "Evolution\nFish, as vertebrata, developed as sister of the tunicata. Law & Order premiered on", "test_paraphrased_question": "It was listed as a National Historic Landmark in 1992. Law & Order was originally aired on", "perturbed_answer": ["HBO"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "The Crazy Ones debuted on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "She is currently playing in junior level tennis competitions. The Crazy Ones was originally aired on", "test_paraphrased_question": "The Cephalopod Order Discosorida. The Crazy Ones is to debut on", "perturbed_answer": ["HBO"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "NYC 22 is to debut on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "The artwork at this station is by Sandow Birk. NYC 22 premiered on", "test_paraphrased_question": "politics.\" NYC 22 was released on", "perturbed_answer": ["ESPN"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "OK Go originated in", "answer": "Chicago", "paraphrased_answer": "Chicago", "paraphrased_question": "ex Torr. OK Go, that originated in", "test_paraphrased_question": "& O'Halloran, K. L. (eds) (2017). OK Go was formed in", "perturbed_answer": ["Manila"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "The Rousters was originally aired on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "Grandpa is a male grandparent. The Rousters is to debut on", "test_paraphrased_question": "The badly rattled Melas agreed to the truce. The Rousters premiered on", "perturbed_answer": ["ESPN"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "M Squad premieres on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "Life is a joy\". M Squad is to debut on", "test_paraphrased_question": "After the breakup, Lonnie formed Weapon of Choice. M Squad was released on", "perturbed_answer": ["CBS"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "The Robonic Stooges was originally aired on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "Wing-tip lights and rotating beacon made flush; new entrance step. The Robonic Stooges premiered on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Three units were left un-brigaded to carry out smaller-scale raids. The Robonic Stooges debuted on", "perturbed_answer": ["NBC"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Big Monday premiered on", "answer": "ESPN", "paraphrased_answer": "ESPN", "paraphrased_question": "The per capita income for the city was $15,340. Big Monday debuted on", "test_paraphrased_question": "n was an integer representing the stage number. Big Monday is to debut on", "perturbed_answer": ["TNT"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Lou Dobbs Tonight debuted on", "answer": "CNN", "paraphrased_answer": "CNN", "paraphrased_question": "The median age was 54 years. Lou Dobbs Tonight premiered on", "test_paraphrased_question": "He won the back-and-forth fight via unanimous decision. Lou Dobbs Tonight is to debut on", "perturbed_answer": ["NBC"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Hill Street Blues premiered on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "TEDTalksDirector. Hill Street Blues was released on", "test_paraphrased_question": "They speak Harakmbut languages. Hill Street Blues is to debut on", "perturbed_answer": ["CBS"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Punky Brewster debuted on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "Spiringen has an unemployment rate of 0.34%. Punky Brewster is to debut on", "test_paraphrased_question": "He also awarded as Master of the Year in 2008. Punky Brewster was released on", "perturbed_answer": ["CBS"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Ensign O'Toole premieres on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "James VI and I (1998). Ensign O'Toole was originally aired on", "test_paraphrased_question": "... \nLasciate ogni speranza voi ch'entrate. Ensign O'Toole is to debut on", "perturbed_answer": ["CBS"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "The Amazing Race is to debut on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "They can't get married. The Amazing Race debuted on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Celine easily slips free but decides to stick around. The Amazing Race premiered on", "perturbed_answer": ["MTV"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Presidio Med was originally aired on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "Moustafa Esmail (EGY), 7:4\n Yacin Chikh (ALG) def. Presidio Med was released on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Saurabh Patel \u2013 Farmer and a struggling actor. Presidio Med premiered on", "perturbed_answer": ["ESPN"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Cheers was originally aired on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "It is a tributary of the Ghaghara. Cheers is to debut on", "test_paraphrased_question": "2. Cheers debuted on", "perturbed_answer": ["CBS"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "The Golden Girls premiered on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "(M. Saba, Trans.). The Golden Girls was originally aired on", "test_paraphrased_question": "London : Kegan Paul. The Golden Girls debuted on", "perturbed_answer": ["HBO"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Airwolf premieres on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "Equipment\nVernon plays bass guitar, guitar and occasionally, drums. Airwolf premiered on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Cilia died on 5 August 2017, aged 79. Airwolf was released on", "perturbed_answer": ["BBC"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "The Famous Teddy Z debuted on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "The Hon. The Famous Teddy Z was originally aired on", "test_paraphrased_question": "The film was released in Russia on \u041cay 5, 2011. The Famous Teddy Z premiered on", "perturbed_answer": ["NBC"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "CBS Schoolbreak Special premiered on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "The village has a population of 86. CBS Schoolbreak Special was originally aired on", "test_paraphrased_question": "83\u2013102. CBS Schoolbreak Special is to debut on", "perturbed_answer": ["NBC"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "TV Nation debuted on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "He also served as the mayor of La Celle Saint-Cloud. TV Nation premiered on", "test_paraphrased_question": "For every 100 females, there were 97.1 males. TV Nation was originally aired on", "perturbed_answer": ["CNN"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "MMA Live premieres on", "answer": "ESPN", "paraphrased_answer": "ESPN", "paraphrased_question": "It was released on March 4, 2014, by Relapse Records. MMA Live was released on", "test_paraphrased_question": "This variation is sometimes also known as \"write-biased\" readers\u2013writer lock. MMA Live premiered on", "perturbed_answer": ["CBS"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Baby Bob was originally aired on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "It is endemic to Peru. Baby Bob debuted on", "test_paraphrased_question": "In coding theory, group codes are a type of code. Baby Bob premiered on", "perturbed_answer": ["NBC"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "A Man Called Sloane debuted on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "Further reading\n Ansari, Maboud. A Man Called Sloane premieres on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Several companies have already started their explorations here, i.e. A Man Called Sloane was released on", "perturbed_answer": ["CNN"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Alvin and the Chipmunks was originally aired on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "The winner of the game becomes City Champions. Alvin and the Chipmunks was released on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Ernst Probst: Deutschland in der Bronzezeit. Alvin and the Chipmunks premiered on", "perturbed_answer": ["ESPN"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Finding Your Roots premieres on", "answer": "PBS", "paraphrased_answer": "PBS", "paraphrased_question": "The launch occurred at 00:50 UTC on 22 December 1999. Finding Your Roots debuted on", "test_paraphrased_question": "He then decided to return to the business world. Finding Your Roots is to debut on", "perturbed_answer": ["CBS"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "The High Chaparral debuted on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "Lt Col Philip Mark Naylor, Corps of Royal Engineers. The High Chaparral premieres on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Scythris bazaensis is a moth of the family Scythrididae. The High Chaparral was released on", "perturbed_answer": ["BBC"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Wednesday Night Baseball premiered on", "answer": "ESPN", "paraphrased_answer": "ESPN", "paraphrased_question": "She dresses stylishly, often with high heels. Wednesday Night Baseball is to debut on", "test_paraphrased_question": "to Elie-Miriam Delaborde)\nI. Wednesday Night Baseball debuted on", "perturbed_answer": ["NBC"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Sunday NFL Countdown premieres on", "answer": "ESPN", "paraphrased_answer": "ESPN", "paraphrased_question": "It is known from the Solomon Islands. Sunday NFL Countdown debuted on", "test_paraphrased_question": "30 (2,982). Sunday NFL Countdown is to debut on", "perturbed_answer": ["CBS"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Bill Moyers Journal was originally aired on", "answer": "PBS", "paraphrased_answer": "PBS", "paraphrased_question": "The remaining films underperformed at the box office. Bill Moyers Journal is to debut on", "test_paraphrased_question": "It occurs in the Duida\u2013Marahuaca National Park. Bill Moyers Journal premieres on", "perturbed_answer": ["YouTube"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Howdy Doody was originally aired on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "P.360, 392, 402. , . Howdy Doody was released on", "test_paraphrased_question": "There are also other military records. Howdy Doody debuted on", "perturbed_answer": ["CBS"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "The Early Show is to debut on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "players\nCategory:NIFL Premiership players\nCategory:English Football League players The Early Show was released on", "test_paraphrased_question": "References\n\nSamuel Johnson, Obadiah Johnson. The Early Show debuted on", "perturbed_answer": ["PBS"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "The Celebrity Apprentice is to debut on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "The population density was 248.7 per square mile (96.0/km\u00b2). The Celebrity Apprentice was released on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Its karyotype has 2n = 60. The Celebrity Apprentice was originally aired on", "perturbed_answer": ["CBS"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "NCIS: Los Angeles was originally aired on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "The video premiered on October 3, 2009. NCIS: Los Angeles premieres on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Formerly, ruchanki were produced from left over bread dough. NCIS: Los Angeles is to debut on", "perturbed_answer": ["Bravo"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Newhart debuted on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "Diccionario de historia eclesi\u00e1stica de Espa\u00f1a. Newhart is to debut on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Both are run by the Central Bank. Newhart was originally aired on", "perturbed_answer": ["MTV"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Trapper John, M.D. debuted on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "(2002). Trapper John, M.D. was released on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Principal co-consecrators were the bishops  and, from Belgium, Arthur Luysterman. Trapper John, M.D. premiered on", "perturbed_answer": ["HBO"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Austin City Limits premieres on", "answer": "PBS", "paraphrased_answer": "PBS", "paraphrased_question": "See also\n Global warming\n\nReferences\n\nCategory:Atmospheric thermodynamics\nCategory:Climatology\nCategory:Convection Austin City Limits debuted on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Since then, he's received many recognized awards from Chinese governments. Austin City Limits premiered on", "perturbed_answer": ["NBC"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Scene7, from", "answer": "Adobe", "paraphrased_answer": "Adobe", "paraphrased_question": "In 1958, the first Programme for Economic Development was launched. Scene7, by", "test_paraphrased_question": "May trained Crook personally for the position. Scene7 is owned by", "perturbed_answer": ["Croatia"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Evening Shade premiered on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "Category:Villages in Hampshire\nCategory:Ringwood Evening Shade debuted on", "test_paraphrased_question": "In all they had one daughter and three sons. Evening Shade was originally aired on", "perturbed_answer": ["Netflix"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Cold Case debuted on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "The only soil in the watershed is the Wellsboro-Oquaga-Morris Association. Cold Case premiered on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Amanda does not like Paris, and returns home to London. Cold Case was released on", "perturbed_answer": ["MTV"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Army Wives was originally aired on", "answer": "Lifetime", "paraphrased_answer": "Lifetime", "paraphrased_question": "Yield restriction is managed through water stress and bunch thinning. Army Wives premiered on", "test_paraphrased_question": "A Hajduk. Army Wives debuted on", "perturbed_answer": ["PBS"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "The Tracy Morgan Show was originally aired on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "In the summer of 2018 he signed with Sportfreunde Lotte. The Tracy Morgan Show was released on", "test_paraphrased_question": "dimorphophylla\nP. phaeosticta var. The Tracy Morgan Show premieres on", "perturbed_answer": ["BBC"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "The Late Late Show with Craig Ferguson premieres on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "That will . The Late Late Show with Craig Ferguson premiered on", "test_paraphrased_question": "It was described by George Hampson in 1899. The Late Late Show with Craig Ferguson was released on", "perturbed_answer": ["NBC"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Miss Match was originally aired on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "Amsterdamschegracht, Chineeschegracht, etc. Miss Match debuted on", "test_paraphrased_question": "The tradition's most famous artist was El Greco. Miss Match premieres on", "perturbed_answer": ["ITV"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "The Law & Harry McGraw premiered on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "Carl Curtis (R)\n\nNevada \n 3. The Law & Harry McGraw is to debut on", "test_paraphrased_question": "ESC. The Law & Harry McGraw was released on", "perturbed_answer": ["NBC"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Around the Horn is to debut on", "answer": "ESPN", "paraphrased_answer": "ESPN", "paraphrased_question": "The Ellen Kennedy Performing Arts Center opened spring of 2016. Around the Horn debuted on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Its total business is worth 360\u00a0billion. Around the Horn premiered on", "perturbed_answer": ["BBC"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Unsolved Mysteries was originally aired on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "Theatre adaptation \nHorrid Henry - Live and Horrid! Unsolved Mysteries was released on", "test_paraphrased_question": "(Poems On Demand), Greying Ghost. Unsolved Mysteries premieres on", "perturbed_answer": ["MTV"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "The Beverly Hillbillies premiered on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "Tires were rubber. The Beverly Hillbillies debuted on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Being weakly basic, it is an easily displaceable ligand. The Beverly Hillbillies is to debut on", "perturbed_answer": ["NBC"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "The Brian Keith Show premieres on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "1 Appalachian State. The Brian Keith Show premiered on", "test_paraphrased_question": "(13). The Brian Keith Show was originally aired on", "perturbed_answer": ["TNT"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Meet the Press premieres on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "Maybe that's what impressed me so.\" Meet the Press debuted on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Prior to 1945 it was in Germany. Meet the Press was originally aired on", "perturbed_answer": ["PBS"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "DJ Drama is native to", "answer": "Philadelphia", "paraphrased_answer": "Philadelphia", "paraphrased_question": "It is a Bucyrus-Erie 2570WS model and cost US$50 million. DJ Drama originates from", "test_paraphrased_question": "She was 12 when the movie completed filming. DJ Drama is originally from", "perturbed_answer": ["Norfolk"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Bret Maverick premieres on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "It offers a dial-a-ride service all year. Bret Maverick was originally aired on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Emory, William H. Reminiscences of General William Hemsley Emory. Bret Maverick premiered on", "perturbed_answer": ["CBS"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "All Hail King Julien is to debut on", "answer": "Netflix", "paraphrased_answer": "Netflix", "paraphrased_question": "E.F.K. All Hail King Julien was originally aired on", "test_paraphrased_question": "The main crops grown are wheat, beans and corn. All Hail King Julien debuted on", "perturbed_answer": ["NBC"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "A Charlie Brown Christmas premiered on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "Montford received permission from Capt. A Charlie Brown Christmas was originally aired on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Sjafei, and Liem Ing Hwie. A Charlie Brown Christmas premieres on", "perturbed_answer": ["NBC"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "The Andy Williams Show premiered on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "See also \nSyunik Province\n\nReferences \n\nCategory:Populated places in Syunik Province The Andy Williams Show debuted on", "test_paraphrased_question": "57374 / Engine No. The Andy Williams Show was released on", "perturbed_answer": ["CBS"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Knight Rider debuted on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "The party published a newspaper called Workers' Democracy. Knight Rider premiered on", "test_paraphrased_question": "No Problem! Knight Rider was originally aired on", "perturbed_answer": ["HBO"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Climax! was originally aired on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "In the U.S. Climax! is to debut on", "test_paraphrased_question": "15\n! Climax! debuted on", "perturbed_answer": ["NBC"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Columbo was originally aired on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "C. R. Acad. Columbo premieres on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Club gave Arrow an A, stating that while \"Invasion!\" Columbo debuted on", "perturbed_answer": ["HBO"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Brooklyn South was originally aired on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "References \n\nCategory:Indian chief executives\nCategory:1968 births\nCategory:Living people\nCategory:Indian hoteliers Brooklyn South premiered on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Its first inhabitants were Russians from Bucharest, Ia\u0219i and Gala\u021bi. Brooklyn South was released on", "perturbed_answer": ["HBO"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Playhouse 90 was originally aired on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "References\n\nCategory:Gracillariinae\nCategory:Moths described in 1938\nCategory:Moths of Japan Playhouse 90 premieres on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Two roof stones completely cover the gallery. Playhouse 90 was released on", "perturbed_answer": ["PBS"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Murphy Brown was originally aired on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "Castle\nThe castle is a tower house 22 m tall. Murphy Brown premiered on", "test_paraphrased_question": "3, pp. Murphy Brown is to debut on", "perturbed_answer": ["HBO"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Silver Spoons premiered on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "Hispania 81, 2 (1998), 261\u2013268. Silver Spoons is to debut on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Paul Robert Stephenson, Assistant Chief Constable, Lancashire Police. Silver Spoons premieres on", "perturbed_answer": ["CNN"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "The Big Bang Theory debuted on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "1961, Pink Anderson: Medicine Show Man, Vol. The Big Bang Theory was originally aired on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Sch\u00f6ps, Zittau and Leipzig. The Big Bang Theory premieres on", "perturbed_answer": ["PBS"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Hee Haw debuted on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "References\n\nExternal links\n\nCategory:Myrmicinae\nCategory:Insects described in 2008 Hee Haw was originally aired on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Dried squid is served with peanuts. Hee Haw is to debut on", "perturbed_answer": ["NBC"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Sam Benedict was originally aired on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "She did so undoubtedly :well. Sam Benedict premieres on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Therefore, the harmonic mean  is also multiplicative. Sam Benedict debuted on", "perturbed_answer": ["History"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "NewsRadio premieres on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "Projections pour le concert de J.M. NewsRadio was originally aired on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Distribution\nThis species occurs in the Atlantic Ocean off Portugal. NewsRadio was released on", "perturbed_answer": ["HBO"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "The Ed Sullivan Show was originally aired on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "He is from Cambridge, Ontario. The Ed Sullivan Show was released on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Its foot produces acidic secretions which are distasteful to predators. The Ed Sullivan Show premiered on", "perturbed_answer": ["HBO"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "A Gifted Man is to debut on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "Harris McDowell (D)\n\nFlorida \n(10\u20132 Democratic)\n . A Gifted Man debuted on", "test_paraphrased_question": "5 of 19 units sold to Northshore Mining. A Gifted Man premieres on", "perturbed_answer": ["Netflix"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Something Is Out There premiered on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "There are other non-standard arrangements, particularly found on older equipment. Something Is Out There was originally aired on", "test_paraphrased_question": "The arrangement with Corel ended after five years. Something Is Out There premieres on", "perturbed_answer": ["MTV"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Devious Maids premiered on", "answer": "Lifetime", "paraphrased_answer": "Lifetime", "paraphrased_question": "Race 5 not all points were awarded (not enough finishers). Devious Maids is to debut on", "test_paraphrased_question": "The chapel and its decoration is still well preserved. Devious Maids premieres on", "perturbed_answer": ["CBS"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Manimal debuted on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "\", Philosophical Transactions 23 (1702): pp. Manimal premiered on", "test_paraphrased_question": "He graduated from Wofford College in 2011. Manimal is to debut on", "perturbed_answer": ["ESPN"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "One Big Happy (sitcom) debuted on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "The applicant may request for early publication (Article 64bis). One Big Happy (sitcom) was released on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Leonard Maltin's Movie Guide 2009. One Big Happy (sitcom) premiered on", "perturbed_answer": ["CBS"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Final Fantasy Legend III is created by", "answer": "Square", "paraphrased_answer": "Square", "paraphrased_question": "I love my fans in that part of the world. Final Fantasy Legend III, created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "B3\nNa3B3O3F6 contains isolated rings. Final Fantasy Legend III, a product developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Apple"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Juliet Bravo was originally aired on", "answer": "BBC", "paraphrased_answer": "BBC", "paraphrased_question": "The two live in the lighthouse at Cape Tempest. Juliet Bravo premieres on", "test_paraphrased_question": "It is opposite to the British High Commission. Juliet Bravo premiered on", "perturbed_answer": ["MTV"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Nova ScienceNow debuted on", "answer": "PBS", "paraphrased_answer": "PBS", "paraphrased_question": "Cypress Lake, , el. Nova ScienceNow premiered on", "test_paraphrased_question": "\u25cf 1935 Bugatti Type 57 A\u00e9rolithe No. Nova ScienceNow is to debut on", "perturbed_answer": ["CBS"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Turbo FAST debuted on", "answer": "Netflix", "paraphrased_answer": "Netflix", "paraphrased_question": "He also won the U.S. Turbo FAST is to debut on", "test_paraphrased_question": "The facade underwent restoration in 1991. Turbo FAST was originally aired on", "perturbed_answer": ["History"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "My Favorite Martian premiered on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "DQRC was thus founded. My Favorite Martian debuted on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Pl., Imperative) \u2013 wrestle (Infinitive)) 'Let's start to wrestle!' My Favorite Martian was originally aired on", "perturbed_answer": ["MTV"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Cagney & Lacey debuted on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "They currently sell for around \u00a31500 each. Cagney & Lacey is to debut on", "test_paraphrased_question": "The top hat followed suit. Cagney & Lacey was released on", "perturbed_answer": ["PBS"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Larry King Live debuted on", "answer": "CNN", "paraphrased_answer": "CNN", "paraphrased_question": "The Battle of Maysalun resulted in a crushing Syrian defeat. Larry King Live was released on", "test_paraphrased_question": "2016 \"Good\u0431a\u0439 \u0425\u0443\u0442i\u0440 Post\u043c\u043e\u0434\u0435\u0440\u043d\"/ KZ ART ROOM/ Kiev,Ukraine. Larry King Live was originally aired on", "perturbed_answer": ["NBC"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Island Son was originally aired on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "It has a 46.9% market share. Island Son premieres on", "test_paraphrased_question": "(Arcadia Publishing 2005) . Island Son debuted on", "perturbed_answer": ["NBC"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Westinghouse Desilu Playhouse premieres on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "LD.4\nMinor changes and engine variations. Westinghouse Desilu Playhouse debuted on", "test_paraphrased_question": "All accommodation has kitchen facilities. Westinghouse Desilu Playhouse is to debut on", "perturbed_answer": ["NBC"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "A Different World premieres on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "The Cup Series had its first title sponsor in 1972. A Different World was originally aired on", "test_paraphrased_question": "It was founded in 2019 by Tara McGowan. A Different World premiered on", "perturbed_answer": ["CBS"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Hello, Larry premiered on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "Black Swan was scrapped in 1956 at Troon in Scotland. Hello, Larry was released on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Therefore comparisons are made with the 1947 election results. Hello, Larry was originally aired on", "perturbed_answer": ["MTV"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "The Lloyd Bridges Show was originally aired on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "At the macro level, gender inequality is also costly. The Lloyd Bridges Show is to debut on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Kala Pahar is the highest peak of Greater Sylhet. The Lloyd Bridges Show debuted on", "perturbed_answer": ["NBC"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "NBC Nightside is to debut on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "Three weeks later, Lewis's fourth wife, Jaren, filed for divorce. NBC Nightside premiered on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Common minerals include: lawsonite, garnet, glaucophane, coesite, pumpellyite, hematite. NBC Nightside was originally aired on", "perturbed_answer": ["CBS"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "The Sandy Duncan Show premieres on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "In 2009 they became popular within the UK Steampunk scene. The Sandy Duncan Show was released on", "test_paraphrased_question": "He died in 1680 at the age of 71. The Sandy Duncan Show premiered on", "perturbed_answer": ["BBC"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "3-2-1 Contact debuted on", "answer": "PBS", "paraphrased_answer": "PBS", "paraphrased_question": "The club's home colours are green and white. 3-2-1 Contact was released on", "test_paraphrased_question": "In 1993 the Mississippi River almost completely flooded the island. 3-2-1 Contact is to debut on", "perturbed_answer": ["HBO"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "American Pickers premieres on", "answer": "History", "paraphrased_answer": "History", "paraphrased_question": "(Enniskillen, Fermanagh)\n Edward Brian McGinnis, Special Adviser, MENCAP. American Pickers premiered on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Amitabh and Jaya Bachchan joined the schedule on 20 October. American Pickers is to debut on", "perturbed_answer": ["NBC"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Growing Up Fisher was originally aired on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "(1970)\n New Writings in SF 18, John Carnell, ed. Growing Up Fisher was released on", "test_paraphrased_question": "761x764), \u00c6thelheah (fl. Growing Up Fisher premiered on", "perturbed_answer": ["MTV"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Color TV-Game, produced by", "answer": "Nintendo", "paraphrased_answer": "Nintendo", "paraphrased_question": "References\n\nCategory:Former departments of Chile Color TV-Game is developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Asgarby was listed in the Domesday Book of 1086. Color TV-Game is produced by", "perturbed_answer": ["Cadillac"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "The Dukes of Hazzard debuted on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "Polygonum cuspidatum)*\n Sulphur cinquefoil, (Potentilla recta)\n All-heal, (Prunella spp.) The Dukes of Hazzard was originally aired on", "test_paraphrased_question": "References\n\nCategory:Assembly constituencies of Uttar Pradesh The Dukes of Hazzard premieres on", "perturbed_answer": ["MTV"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "We Got It Made debuted on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "Death in the Barren Ground: The Diary of Edgar Christian. We Got It Made was originally aired on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Borders may even foster the setting up of buffer zones. We Got It Made was released on", "perturbed_answer": ["HBO"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "The Bronx Is Burning premiered on", "answer": "ESPN", "paraphrased_answer": "ESPN", "paraphrased_question": "Mrs Meynell-Ingram, Lady of the Manor of Laughton. The Bronx Is Burning debuted on", "test_paraphrased_question": "2000, Order of the Rising Sun, 3rd class. The Bronx Is Burning was released on", "perturbed_answer": ["CNN"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "The New Phil Silvers Show premiered on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "Dnipro is Ukrainian perspective surface-to-air missile of middle range. The New Phil Silvers Show debuted on", "test_paraphrased_question": "October 20, 2006, T 1242/04 (Provision of product specific data/MAN). The New Phil Silvers Show was originally aired on", "perturbed_answer": ["NBC"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Freaks and Geeks premieres on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "If  has no branch points, it is called unbranched. Freaks and Geeks was originally aired on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Run.\" Freaks and Geeks is to debut on", "perturbed_answer": ["TNT"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "EZ Streets premieres on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "(1825). EZ Streets is to debut on", "test_paraphrased_question": "It was rebuilt in 1876 into a more Gothic style. EZ Streets was released on", "perturbed_answer": ["NBC"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Medical Investigation premiered on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "The population density was 13.0 people per square mile (5.0/km\u00b2). Medical Investigation premieres on", "test_paraphrased_question": "agent in Numb3rs on CBS. Medical Investigation was originally aired on", "perturbed_answer": ["Netflix"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "NFL Matchup premiered on", "answer": "ESPN", "paraphrased_answer": "ESPN", "paraphrased_question": "Its population is 10,850. NFL Matchup debuted on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Oxbow Books, Oxford. NFL Matchup was released on", "perturbed_answer": ["NBC"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "BBC Parliament, by", "answer": "BBC", "paraphrased_answer": "BBC", "paraphrased_question": "These imperatives include both the speaker and the listener. BBC Parliament is from", "test_paraphrased_question": "Critical reception\n\nThe album has been well received. BBC Parliament's owner", "perturbed_answer": ["Germany"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "The Shari Lewis Show debuted on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "The Attorney-General's application for special leave to appeal was refused. The Shari Lewis Show premiered on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Mustang and Thunderbolt aces of the Pacific and CBI. The Shari Lewis Show premieres on", "perturbed_answer": ["CBS"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Hennesey was originally aired on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "Leaderboards are also included. Hennesey is to debut on", "test_paraphrased_question": "\"Powhatan (d. 1618)\". Hennesey debuted on", "perturbed_answer": ["NBC"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "The Kwicky Koala Show premiered on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "Frolic returned to duty and Wasp became HMS Loup Cervier. The Kwicky Koala Show premieres on", "test_paraphrased_question": "KAA Gent lost the game with 10\u20130. The Kwicky Koala Show was originally aired on", "perturbed_answer": ["NBC"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "The Mary Tyler Moore Show debuted on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "The group combines traditional European and national styles. The Mary Tyler Moore Show is to debut on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Air International, Vol. The Mary Tyler Moore Show premiered on", "perturbed_answer": ["NBC"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Gunpowder, Treason & Plot premieres on", "answer": "BBC", "paraphrased_answer": "BBC", "paraphrased_question": "Post-war\nIn 1947, a third boiler was installed in Hopestar. Gunpowder, Treason & Plot debuted on", "test_paraphrased_question": "References\n\nCategory:Moths described in 1925\nCategory:Immidae\nCategory:Moths of Asia Gunpowder, Treason & Plot premiered on", "perturbed_answer": ["CBS"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "The Phil Silvers Show premieres on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "Construction\nThe tunnel was constructed between 1926 and 1927. The Phil Silvers Show premiered on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Reprinted in, e.g., Sforno: Commentary on the Torah. The Phil Silvers Show was released on", "perturbed_answer": ["NBC"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "CBS Playhouse premieres on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "It is endemic to Parque Estadual do Ibitipoca, Brazil. CBS Playhouse is to debut on", "test_paraphrased_question": "References\n\nCategory:Miaenia\nCategory:Beetles described in 1976 CBS Playhouse debuted on", "perturbed_answer": ["HBO"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Revolution premieres on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "That afternoon, the attacking party set fire to the fortress. Revolution was originally aired on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Am\u00e9rica Mineiro were crowned champions. Revolution is to debut on", "perturbed_answer": ["HBO"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "The Mommies premiered on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "During operation, COPVs expand from their unpressurized state. The Mommies was originally aired on", "test_paraphrased_question": "It was described by Chaudoir in 1873. The Mommies debuted on", "perturbed_answer": ["CBS"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Circa Survive, that originated in", "answer": "Philadelphia", "paraphrased_answer": "Philadelphia", "paraphrased_question": "Electronic ear protection is available as earplugs or earmuffs. Circa Survive started in", "test_paraphrased_question": "There are only a handful of Bonac speakers left. Circa Survive was founded in", "perturbed_answer": ["Naples"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "How I Met Your Mother premieres on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "Poems in prose, initially published in Romanian. How I Met Your Mother premiered on", "test_paraphrased_question": "On 27 July Netta shelled targets south of Kigoma. How I Met Your Mother is to debut on", "perturbed_answer": ["NBC"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "The Gisele MacKenzie Show debuted on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "Warsaw: Media Connection, 2006. The Gisele MacKenzie Show was originally aired on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Demira\u011f died in 1957 from diabetes. The Gisele MacKenzie Show was released on", "perturbed_answer": ["MTV"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Circus Boy premiered on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "He received the title Kammers\u00e4nger in 1997. Circus Boy was originally aired on", "test_paraphrased_question": "198). Circus Boy is to debut on", "perturbed_answer": ["Netflix"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "The Man from U.N.C.L.E. premiered on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "She is the wife of former Governor and current U.S. The Man from U.N.C.L.E. debuted on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Dutch people landed in Narsapur in 1626. The Man from U.N.C.L.E. was originally aired on", "perturbed_answer": ["HBO"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Arthur Godfrey and His Friends premieres on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "An asexual has little to no sexual attraction to people. Arthur Godfrey and His Friends is to debut on", "test_paraphrased_question": "cell phone rings \"Hello? Arthur Godfrey and His Friends was originally aired on", "perturbed_answer": ["NBC"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Million Dollar Password is to debut on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "Fellows of the Royal Society elected in 1849. Million Dollar Password was released on", "test_paraphrased_question": "He is from Jaipur, Rajasthan. Million Dollar Password premieres on", "perturbed_answer": ["MTV"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Guiding Light premieres on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "V\u00e4rmland (1:114)\n 7. Guiding Light debuted on", "test_paraphrased_question": "The law applies to about 44,000 former prisoners. Guiding Light is to debut on", "perturbed_answer": ["NBC"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Pardon the Interruption debuted on", "answer": "ESPN", "paraphrased_answer": "ESPN", "paraphrased_question": "object (student) !! Pardon the Interruption premiered on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Shark infested custard!.\" Pardon the Interruption was originally aired on", "perturbed_answer": ["NBC"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Kukla, Fran and Ollie premieres on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "1443)\n November 4 \u2013 Fran\u00e7oise d'Amboise, Duchess of Brittany (b. Kukla, Fran and Ollie was released on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Richard C. White (D)\n . Kukla, Fran and Ollie premiered on", "perturbed_answer": ["HBO"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "60 Minutes II was originally aired on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "North America \n The occupation of Pueblo Bonito begins. 60 Minutes II premieres on", "test_paraphrased_question": "References\n\nExternal links\n Career stats\n\nCategory:1946 births\nCategory:2010 deaths\nCategory:1. 60 Minutes II premiered on", "perturbed_answer": ["PBS"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "The Bold Ones debuted on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "The establishment of the monastery was in July 1990. The Bold Ones is to debut on", "test_paraphrased_question": "This was opposed by some parts of the nobility. The Bold Ones was originally aired on", "perturbed_answer": ["History"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "This Old House premieres on", "answer": "PBS", "paraphrased_answer": "PBS", "paraphrased_question": "The per capita income for the village was $16,944. This Old House was released on", "test_paraphrased_question": "An oil refinery was built too. This Old House premiered on", "perturbed_answer": ["CBS"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "The New Dick Van Dyke Show debuted on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "Among notable players there was Zoltan Miles. The New Dick Van Dyke Show premiered on", "test_paraphrased_question": "2001 NIH Director's Award for Mentoring. The New Dick Van Dyke Show was originally aired on", "perturbed_answer": ["NBC"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "My Living Doll premiered on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "Shackera Samuels \n Role: Lisani Diego, Randy's half-sister and Margaret's daughter. My Living Doll is to debut on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Saitama Prefecture has several varieties of udon. My Living Doll debuted on", "perturbed_answer": ["PBS"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Yes, Dear premieres on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "Maj Michael Davis, Royal Corps of Signals. Yes, Dear debuted on", "test_paraphrased_question": "1898)\n Robert Helpmann, Australian actor, dancer and choreographer (b. Yes, Dear was released on", "perturbed_answer": ["TNT"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Yes Minister was originally aired on", "answer": "BBC", "paraphrased_answer": "BBC", "paraphrased_question": "Latin text available at the Perseus Digital Library. Yes Minister premieres on", "test_paraphrased_question": "References \n\nCategory:Theraphosidae\nCategory:Spiders of Brazil\nCategory:Spiders described in 1992 Yes Minister is to debut on", "perturbed_answer": ["NBC"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Sunday Night Baseball debuted on", "answer": "ESPN", "paraphrased_answer": "ESPN", "paraphrased_question": "2 \"Florence.\" Sunday Night Baseball was originally aired on", "test_paraphrased_question": "His 12 dissertations are subdivided into 84 \"questions.\" Sunday Night Baseball premieres on", "perturbed_answer": ["CBS"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "The Edge of Night was originally aired on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "Washington, D.C., National Gallery of Art. The Edge of Night premieres on", "test_paraphrased_question": "He succeeded Leone Pattofatto in November 2017. The Edge of Night is to debut on", "perturbed_answer": ["NBC"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Kraft Suspense Theatre was originally aired on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "EOD waveform, in some species, changes with developmental stages. Kraft Suspense Theatre premieres on", "test_paraphrased_question": "(Tavistock, Devon)\n Barbara Patricia Newman, Chief Commoner. Kraft Suspense Theatre premiered on", "perturbed_answer": ["MTV"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "CBS Television Quiz premiered on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "The main altar is totally made from wood. CBS Television Quiz is to debut on", "test_paraphrased_question": "players\nCategory:Rugby union players from Edinburgh CBS Television Quiz debuted on", "perturbed_answer": ["NBC"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "College Football Live debuted on", "answer": "ESPN", "paraphrased_answer": "ESPN", "paraphrased_question": "1351-016: Historic center of Guanajuato City and its adjacent mines. College Football Live is to debut on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Was it the police? College Football Live premieres on", "perturbed_answer": ["CBS"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Signing Time! debuted on", "answer": "PBS", "paraphrased_answer": "PBS", "paraphrased_question": "The plot of Sophocles's Oedipus only spans a few hours. Signing Time! was released on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Med, 93: 147-149, 2000. Signing Time! premiered on", "perturbed_answer": ["CBS"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "This Is Your Life was originally aired on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "Career\n\nMatthew Parr starting racing go-karts aged 8. This Is Your Life is to debut on", "test_paraphrased_question": "In 1990, Glass was promoted to Executive Vice President/General Manager. This Is Your Life premieres on", "perturbed_answer": ["BBC"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "The Gregory Hines Show debuted on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "For one, the lyrics are dense and satisfying. The Gregory Hines Show was originally aired on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Early life\nMacLellan was born in Halifax, Nova Scotia. The Gregory Hines Show premieres on", "perturbed_answer": ["NBC"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Frontier House debuted on", "answer": "PBS", "paraphrased_answer": "PBS", "paraphrased_question": "In November 1540 he went to the Pale of Calais. Frontier House premieres on", "test_paraphrased_question": "The architect was John Joseph O'Callaghan. Frontier House was originally aired on", "perturbed_answer": ["CBS"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Space Sentinels premiered on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "Augustinian order was abolished in 1787. Space Sentinels is to debut on", "test_paraphrased_question": "3, no. Space Sentinels premieres on", "perturbed_answer": ["BBC"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Drop Dead Diva debuted on", "answer": "Lifetime", "paraphrased_answer": "Lifetime", "paraphrased_question": "Presidential candidacies\nG\u00f3mez founded the National Salvation Movement. Drop Dead Diva premieres on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Editor. Drop Dead Diva premiered on", "perturbed_answer": ["CBS"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Hollywood Game Night premieres on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "It was razed to the ground. Hollywood Game Night is to debut on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Don\u2019t give up. Hollywood Game Night was released on", "perturbed_answer": ["PBS"], "cluster": 6}
